<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata>
    <idinfo>
        <citation>
            <citeinfo>
                <title>CT20FIP23CSA</title>
                <geoform>vector digital data</geoform>
            </citeinfo>
        </citation>
        <descript>
            <abstract>This data is the product of 2020 census tracts split by 2023 incorporated city boundaries and unincorporated community/countywide statistical areas (CSA) boundaries. The census tract boundaries have been altered and aligned where necessary with legal city boundaries and unincorporated areas, including along shoreline/coastal areas. This data is also known as the Split Tract data. This data can be used to estimate population changes over time. Census Tract:Every 10 years the Census Bureau counts the population of the United States as mandated by Constitution. The Census Bureau released 2020 geographic boundaries data including census tracts for the analysis and mapping of demographic information across the United States. City Boundary:City Boundary data is the base map information for the County of Los Angeles. These City Boundaries are based on the Los Angeles County Seamless Cadastral Landbase. The Landbase is jointly maintained by the Los Angeles County Assessor and the Los Angeles County Department of Public Works (DPW). This layer represents current city boundaries within Los Angeles County. The DPW provides the most current shapefiles representing city boundaries and city annexations. True, legal boundaries are only determined on the ground by surveyors licensed in the State of California.Countywide Statistical Areas (CSA): The countywide Statistical Area (CSA) was defined to provide a common geographic boundary for reporting departmental statistics for unincorporated areas and incorporated Los Angeles city to the Board of Supervisors. The CSA boundary and CSA names are established by the CIO and the LA County Enterprise GIS group worked with the Los Angeles County Board of Supervisors Unincorporated Area and Field Deputies that reflect as best as possible the general name preferences of residents and historical names of areas. This data is primarily focused on broad statistics and reporting, not mapping of communities. This data is not designed to perfectly represent communities, nor jurisdictional boundaries such as Angeles National Forest. CSA represent board approved geographies comprised of Census block groups split by cities.Data Field:CT20FIP23CSA: ID field (combination of 2020 census tract number, 2023 city FIP code and CSA name)CT20: 2020 Census TractFIP23: FIP code for legal cityCITY: Legal City Name (as of July 1, 2023)CSA: Countywide Statistical Area (CSA) and Los Angeles City neighborhood namesHow this data created?This polygon data is created by intersecting 2020 census tract polygons, LA Country City neighborhood polygons and Countywide Statistical Areas (CSA) data polygon. The resulting polygon boundary aligned and matched with the legal city boundary whenever possible. Updates:2023 December: Merged &amp;quot;Unincorporated Charter Oak&amp;quot; (south of 10 freeway) into &amp;quot;Unincorporated Covina&amp;quot; polygon, census tract 4063.00.2023 July: The major updates include 2022 November Santa Clarita City annexation and Kinneloa Mesa community (previously it was a part of Unincorporated East Pasdena). This data also aligns with current city boundary along LA County shoreline areas. </abstract>
            <purpose>This polygon data is the product of 2020 census tract boundaries split by LA County legal city boundaries and unincorporated areas (commonly known as CSA) as of December, 2023.</purpose>
        </descript>
        <spdom>
            <bounding>
                <westbc>-118.953451</westbc>
                <eastbc>-117.644097</eastbc>
                <northbc>34.823531</northbc>
                <southbc>32.796714</southbc>
            </bounding>
        </spdom>
        <keywords>
            <theme>
                <themekt>None</themekt>
                <themekey>Legal City</themekey>
                <themekey>City</themekey>
                <themekey>Incorporated City</themekey>
                <themekey>Unincorporated Area</themekey>
                <themekey>Census Tract</themekey>
                <themekey>Tracts</themekey>
                <themekey>Split Census Tract</themekey>
            </theme>
        </keywords>
        <accconst>None</accconst>
        <useconst>This data is for demographic tabulation purposes only and may not have been prepared for or be suitable for geoprocessing analysis, and/or for legal, engineering, or surveying intents. Users of this information should review or consult the primary data and information sources to ascertain the usability of the information.The County of Los Angeles provides this data with no claim as to the completeness, usefulness, or accuracy of its content, positional or otherwise. The user hereby acknowledges that the data is subject to change and that its accuracy cannot be guaranteed. The County and its officials and employees make no warranty, express or implied, and assume no legal liability or responsibility for the ability of users to fulfill their intended purposes in accessing or using this data. The data could include technical inaccuracies and typographical errors. The data is presented "as is," without warranty of any kind, including, but not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement. </useconst>
        <datacred>Census Bureau, Los Angeles County Internal Services Department (ISD), Los Angeles County Department of Public Work (DPW).
This polygon boundary data is created by ISD - GIS Section.</datacred>
        <native> Version 6.2 (Build 9200) ; Esri ArcGIS 10.9.1.28388</native>
    </idinfo>
    <spdoinfo>
        <direct>Vector</direct>
        <ptvctinf>
            <sdtsterm>
                <sdtstype>GT-polygon composed of chains</sdtstype>
                <ptvctcnt>2881</ptvctcnt>
            </sdtsterm>
        </ptvctinf>
    </spdoinfo>
    <eainfo>
        <detailed>
            <enttyp>
                <enttypl>CT20FIP23CSA</enttypl>
            </enttyp>
            <attr>
                <attrlabl>OBJECTID</attrlabl>
                <attrdef>Internal feature number.</attrdef>
                <attrdefs>Esri</attrdefs>
                <attrdomv>
                                        
                    <udom>Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom>
                                    
                </attrdomv>
            </attr>
            <attr>
                <attrlabl>Shape</attrlabl>
                <attrdef>Feature geometry.</attrdef>
                <attrdefs>Esri</attrdefs>
                <attrdomv>
                                        
                    <udom>Coordinates defining the features.</udom>
                                    
                </attrdomv>
            </attr>
            <attr>
                <attrlabl>CT20</attrlabl>
            </attr>
            <attr>
                <attrlabl>FIP23</attrlabl>
            </attr>
            <attr>
                <attrlabl>CITY</attrlabl>
            </attr>
            <attr>
                <attrlabl>CSA</attrlabl>
            </attr>
            <attr>
                <attrlabl>CT20FIP23CSA</attrlabl>
            </attr>
            <attr>
                <attrlabl>Shape_Length</attrlabl>
                <attrdef>Length of feature in internal units.</attrdef>
                <attrdefs>Esri</attrdefs>
                <attrdomv>
                                        
                    <udom>Positive real numbers that are automatically generated.</udom>
                                    
                </attrdomv>
            </attr>
            <attr>
                <attrlabl>Shape_Area</attrlabl>
                <attrdef>Area of feature in internal units squared.</attrdef>
                <attrdefs>Esri</attrdefs>
                <attrdomv>
                                        
                    <udom>Positive real numbers that are automatically generated.</udom>
                                    
                </attrdomv>
            </attr>
        </detailed>
    </eainfo>
    <metainfo>
        <metd>20230927</metd>
        <metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
        <metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
        <mettc>local time</mettc>
    </metainfo>
</metadata>
